The	O
children	O
were	O
alone	O
when	O
searchers	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
are	O
now	DATE
receiving	O
medical	O
attention	O
,	O
President	TITLE
Gustavo	PERSON
Petro	PERSON
told	O
reporters	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
to	O
Bogota	CITY
from	O
Cuba	COUNTRY
,	O
where	O
he	O
signed	O
a	O
cease	O
fire	CAUSE_OF_DEATH
agreement	O
with	O
representatives	O
of	O
the	O
National	ORGANIZATION
Liberation	ORGANIZATION
Army	ORGANIZATION
rebel	O
group	O
.	O
