On	O
the	O
heels	O
of	O
a	O
recent	O
travel	O
advisory	O
issued	O
for	O
Jamaica	COUNTRY
by	O
the	O
US	ORGANIZATION
State	ORGANIZATION
Department	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Tourism	TITLE
Minister	TITLE
Edmond	PERSON
Bartlett	PERSON
is	O
headed	O
to	O
the	O
North	MISC
American	NATIONALITY
country	O
to	O
seek	O
to	O
assure	O
travellers	O
that	O
the	O
island	O
is	O
a	O
"	O
safe	O
,	O
secure	O
and	O
seamless	O
"	O
destination	O
.	O
